(Amy:)Do you know him?
(Dave:)No, but I've followed
his work for years.
(Dave:)He's a rock star.
(Dave:)You've got to
tell me about him.
(Dave:)What's he like?
(door opens)
He really seems into her.
(Bernadette:)I took a video.
(Bernadette:)I forgot how much
fun this is.
(Leonard:)Okay, we saw them.
(Leonard:)Can we go catch the movie?
(Penny sighs)
Why'd you bring him?
(Penny:)I had to; we're married now.
(Bernadette:)Ugh, I hear that.
(Dave:)I'm sorry, just one more
question about Sheldon.
(Amy:)Sure, why not?
(Dave:)It's more of a four-part
question, really.
(Dave:)When he wrote his paper on
supersingular prime numbers,
(Dave:)how long did it take?
(Amy:)Um... about an hour and half.
Wow!
I mean, wow!
(Dave:)And you were
there to see it?
(Amy:)Yes. Yep. We were on a date.